[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The dodo was able to grow so large and become flightless because of the lack of natural predators on the island it inhabited.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a medical term that refers to crying?", "correct_answer": "Lacrimation", "incorrect_answers": ["Humoring", "Lactation", "Blepharitis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Calvin Klein won the Coty Award, the most prestigious award in fashion, in what three consecutive years?", "correct_answer": "1973, 1974, 1975", "incorrect_answers": ["1970, 1971, 1972", "1972, 1973, 1974", "1974, 1975, 1976"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Blackjack what card combination is called Blackjack?", "correct_answer": "An ace and a card with value 10", "incorrect_answers": ["Any card combination with total value of 21", "An ace and a jack", "Two aces"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Alfred Hitchcock movie was voted the greatest thriller movie of all time, and the 14th best movie ever made, by the American Film Institute?", "correct_answer": "Psycho", "incorrect_answers": ["The Birds", "Strangers on a Train", "Rear Window"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these people would be able to successfully combine their regimes with a low carb diet without having to violate one of them?", "correct_answer": "A vegetarian", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "A vegan", "A fruitarian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital and largest city of Italy?", "correct_answer": "Rome", "incorrect_answers": ["Milan", "Genoa", "Venice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1957 Major John Glenn, Jr. set an air speed record for the trip from California to New York. How long did the trip take?", "correct_answer": "3 hours 23 minutes 8.4 seconds", "incorrect_answers": ["2 hours 19 minutes 4.8 seconds", "1 hours 21 minutes 4.8 seconds", "1 hour 56 minutes 8.4 seconds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cats are so curious because they are always looking for food.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Two of the stuntmen in the movie The Wild Bunch were Tap and Joe Canutt. What was the first name of their father who was also a stuntman?", "correct_answer": "Yakima", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow Cloud", "George", "Terence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tic-tac-toe is the American name of which popular paper and pencil game?", "correct_answer": "Noughts and crosses", "incorrect_answers": ["Sprouts", "Gomoku", "Strategio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Japanese car brand is among the largest automobile producers on the planet. It was founded in 1909 under a slightly different name.", "correct_answer": "Suzuki", "incorrect_answers": ["Mazda", "Isuzu", "Nissan"]}]